<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="0.4 Ultimate Care of the Facility"
    id="0f41a9d2-a707-4969-9fb7-b19c89226d11"
    documentation="All of these become &quot;management&quot; processes from &quot;manager&quot; position.&#xA;&#xA;Demand Manager&#xA;Business Relationship Manager - maintains relationships gverned by contracts.&#xA;FInancial Manager - managing budgeting, accounting, and changing requirements&#xA;IT steering group - sets direction for management and it services (NCSA would have a set within this group focusing on NCOA's it services, strategy and interaction)&#xA;Service portfolio manager - not quite an architect who's portfolio (duties) oriented&#xA;!Service Strategy Manager – supports the development of service providers strategy, communicates and implements it.&#xA;&#xA;______&#xA;Service design&#xA;Applicaations analyst - deals with payloads and infrastructure. performs an analyst funtion.&#xA;!Availability Manager - records IT service availability, analyzies and improves it and meet availability requirements. - does it work? (the main position within SERVICE DESIGN)&#xA;!Capacity manager - almost the same person as availability manager. Knows possible capacity. how much can it take?&#xA;Compliance mananager - legal and compliance overwatch.&#xA;!Enterprise architect - works with NCOA, maintains company structure. (See Harmonious Tech Integration)&#xA;!Infosec manager - roleof CSO&#xA;!IT Service continuity manger - a parent position of infosec that also includes disaster recovery. &#xA;!Risk manager - identifies risks.&#xA;Service cata - maintains the Service Catalog. (can make architect do this)&#xA;Service level manager -  ensures that service-lvl agreements are met adn that supporting services are adequate. &#xA;Service Owner - owns a particular service.&#xA;!Supplier Manager - ensures good value for supplier contracts. Part of Caylin's job. A role assigned to IT Financial Manager.&#xA;!Technical Analyst - similar to application analyst. Analyzes company IT.&#xA;______________&#xA;Service Transition&#xA;Application Developer - develops apps and systems&#xA;!Change Advisory Board - advise change managers on changes and how important they are.&#xA;!Change Manager - controls the lifecycle of all chnages. Ensures minimum disruption to it services. Important to Database Manager.&#xA;!Config Manager - maintains onfiguration items needed by IT services. maintains the logical model. &#xA;Emergency Change Advisory Board - subset of Change Advisory Board thta makes high-impact Emergency Changes. Flexible membership.&#xA;!Knowlege Manager - manages information by providing the learnign and info framework. The StackExchange master. Reduces the need to rediscover knowlege. &#xA;!Project Manager - plans and coordinaates the resources to deploy releases.&#xA;!Release manager - decides what gets released into the &quot;public&quot; and what doesn't in teerms of complete or intermediate product. &#xA;Test manager - verifies that the systems are ready for the release. Manages the intensity of the testing based on criticality of the release.&#xA;________________&#xA;Continual Service Improvement&#xA;!Continual Service Improvement Manager manages improvements to IT infrastructure performance &#xA;!Process Architect creates the processes, changes them and lets them coopeeraate, builds model. &#xA;!Process Owner executes processes by ensuring their fitness for stakeholder activities.&#xA;"/>
